Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- Trist, Eric "Improving" - United States General Accounting Office., Publication (Box 25)
  - Tsuda, Masumi, "Human Resource Development and New Technology in the Automobile Industry--The Japanese Case", Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Human Resource Development and New Technology in the Automobile Industry- The Japanese Case, 1984; Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Author: Masumi Tsuda
  - Tsujino, Hiroshi, "Collective Bargaining in Japan: Recent Trends and Problems", Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in Japan: Recent Trends and Problems, 1987; Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
      Author: Hiroshi Tsujino
  - Tsumari, Yoshi and Rebecca R. Tsumari, "A New Mechanism of employment Adjustment in the U.S.", Publication (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: A New Mechanism of Employment Adjustment in the U.S., 1984; Publication (Box 25, Folder 14)
      Author: Yoshi Tsumuri and Rebecca R. Tsumuri
  - Turnball, Peter J., "Trade Unions and Productivity", Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Trade Unions and Productivity, 1991; Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
      Author: Peter J. Turnbull
    - Item 2: What's in a Name: Playing Hide and Seek with QWL, 1985; Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
      Author: Hans Van Beinum
  - Turney, John R. and Stanley L. Cohen, "Participative Management: What is the Right Level?", Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Participative Management: What is the Right Level?, 1980; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
      Author: John R. Turney and Stanley L. Cohen
    - Item 2: Dutch 'Task Groups', 1991; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
      Author: Rob van der Moolen
  - Tuttle, Thomas C., Productivity Measurement Methods: Classification, Critique, and Implications for the Air Force, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Productivity Measurement Methods: Classification, Critique and Implications for the Air Force, 1981; Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
      Author: Thomas C. Tuttle
  - Twelve Commonsense Steps to Productivity, Publication (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Twelve Commonsense Steps to Productivity, 1983; Publication (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Tynan, Oliver, "Change and the Nature of Work: Some Employment and Organizational Problems of AMT", Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Change and the Nature of Work: Some Employment and Organizational Problems of AMT, 1984; Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
      Author: Oliver Tynan
  - Tynan, Oliver, Improving the Quality of Working Life in the 1980's, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Improving the Quality of Working Life in the 1980's, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Tynan, Oliver, "Volvo Revisited", Publication (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Volvo Revisited, 1984; Publication (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Uhlenberg, Joan "Integrating Quality Into Marketing and Sales", Publication (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Integrating Quality Into Marketing and Sales, 1991; Publication (Box 25, Folder 22)
      Author: Joan Uhlenberg
  - Ullman, Joseph C., "Learning More About People's Values May Make You a Better Manager", Publication (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Learning More About People's Values May Make You a Better Manager, 1987; Publication (Box 25, Folder 23)
      Author: Joseph C. Ullman
  - United Automobile Workers, Alcohol and Drug Abuse Recovery Program, Publication (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Alcohol and Drug Abuse Recovery Program, Publication (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - United Auto Workers, Economic Dislocation: A Guide for UWA Representatives to the Job Training and Partnership Act of 1982, Publication (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Economic Dislocation: A Guide for UAW Representatives to the Job Training and Partnership Act, Publication (Box 25, Folder 25)
      Author: United Auto Workers
  - UAW-Ford National Joint Committee on Employee Involvement, Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: EI: UAW-Ford Employee Involvement Handbook II: Concepts and Ideas for Continuing Progress, 1983; Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - United Mine Workers of America, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Breaking the Trust: The Pittston Company's Drive to Break Appalachia's Coalfield Communities, 1989; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
      Author: United Mine Workers of America
  - U.S. Catholic Conference, "Second Draft: Catholic Social Teaching and the U.S. Economy", Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Second Draft: Catholic Social Teaching and the U.S. Economy, 1985; Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - U.S. Chamber of Commerce "U.S. International Competitiveness in the 1990s: Where Do We Stand?", Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: U.S. International Competitiveness in the 1990s: Where do we stand?, 1992; Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce, Coping with the Loss of a Major Employer: A How-to Manual, Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Coping with the Loss of a Major Employer: A How-to-Manual, 1979; Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
      Author: U.S. Department of Commerce
  - U.S. Department of Commerce, Foreign Directo Investment in the United States: Annual Survey Results, Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Annual Survey Results, 1984; Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce, Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Operations of U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies Revised 1982, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Operations of U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies, 1985; Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce, Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Operations of U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies Revised 1983, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Operations of U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies Revised 1983 Estimates, 1986; Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce, Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Operations of U.S. Affiliates of Foreign Companies Preliminary 1984 Estimates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Foreign Direct Investment in the United States: Operations of Affiliates of Foreign Companies Preliminary 1984 Estimates, 1986; Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce, Productivity Improvements, Your Guide to Today's Resources, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: Productivity Improvements: Your Guide to Today's Resources, 1984; Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Department of Education. America 2000: An Education Strategy, Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: America 2000: An Education Strategy, 1991; Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, "A Proposed Program for Encouraging Labor-Management Committees and Other Work Place Innovations", Publication (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: A Proposed Program for Encouraging Labor-Management Committees and Other Work Place Innovations, 1979; Publication (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Admission and Apprenticeship in the Building Trades Industry, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Admission and Apprenticeship in the Building Trades Industry, 1971; Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, U.S. Dept. of Education, and the U.S. Dept. of Commerce, Building a Quality Workforce, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Building a Quality Workforce, 1988; Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Employee Relations Bibliography: Public, Non-Profit and Professional Employment, 1967-1977, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Employee Relations Bibliography: Public, Non-Profit and Professional Employment, 1978; Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Exclusive Union Work Referral Systems in the Building Trades, Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Exclusive Union Work Referral Systems in the Building Trades, 1970; Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - US DOL BLMRCP, Publication (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Film/Video Sourcebook for Cooperative and Employee Involvement Programs, 1985; Publication (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, "Labor-Management Relations and Restructuring Schools", Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Relations and Restructuring Schools, 1991; Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, "Improving Productivity and the Quality of Working Life Through Labor-Management Committees and Other Innovations in Work Organization", Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Improving Productivity and the Quality of Working Life through Labor-Management Committees and Other Innovations in Work Organization, 1979; Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Jobs For the Future, Publication (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Jobs for the Future, 1988; Publication (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, A Report on the Glass Ceiling Initiative, Publication (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: A Report on the Glass Ceiling Intitiative, 1992; Publication (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Summary of JTLS Data for JTPA Title IIA Enrollment and Terminations, Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Summary of JTLS Data for JTPA Title IIA Enrollment and Terminations, 1985; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Summary of Public Sector Labor Relations Policies, Publication (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Summary of Public Sector Labor Relations Policies, 1976; Publication (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Survey of Employer Anti-Drug Programs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Survey of Employer Anti-Drug Programs, 1989; Publication (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, and the U.S. Dept. of Education, The Bottom Line: Basic Skills in the Work Place, Publication (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: The Bottom Line: Basic Skills in the Workplace, 1988; Publication (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, The Use of Economic Data in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: The Use of Economic Data in Collective Bargaining, 1978; Publication (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - U.S. Department of Labor and American Women in Radio and Television, Inc., Women on the Job: Careers in the Electronic Media, Publication (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Women on the Job: Careers in the Electronic Media, 1990; Publication (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Workforce Quality: Perspectives from the U.S. and Japan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Workforce Quality: Perspectives from the U.S. and Japan, 1991; Publication (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, Working in America: A Chart Book, Publication (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: Working in America: A Chart Book, 1988; Publication (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation and the U.S. Navy, The National Shipbuilding Program: Problem Solving Teams in Shipbuilding, Publication (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: The National Shipbuilding Program: Problem-solving Teams in Shipbuilding, 1986; Publication (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation and the U.S. Navy, The National Shipbuilding Program: Problem Solving Teams in Shipbuilding, Publication (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: The National Shipbuilding Program: Problem Solving Teams in Shipbuilding, 1988; Publication (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - U.S. Department of Treasury "Report to the Congress on International Economic and Exchange Rate Policy", Publication (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: Report to the Congress on International Economic and Exchange Rate Policy, 1988; Publication (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - U.S. Department of Treasury, A Study of Labor Management Relations in the Internal Revenue Service, Publication (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Item 1: A Study of Labor Management Relations in the Internal Revenue Service, 1982; Publication (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Alternative Work Schedules for Federal Employees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: Alternative Work Schedules for Federal Employees, 1985; Publication (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Gainsharing: DOD Efforts Highlight and Effective Tool for Enhancing Productivity, Publication (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: Gainsharing: DOD Efforts Highlight an Effective Tool for Enhancing Productivity, 1986; Publication (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Employee Involvement: Issues for Agencies to Consider in Designing and Implementing Programs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Item 1: Employee Involvement: Issues for Agencies to Consider in Designing and Implementing Programs, 1988; Publication (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Employment Service: Variations in Local Office Performance, Publication (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: Employment Service: Variations in Local Office Performance, 1989; Publication (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Human Resource Management: Status of Agency Practices for Improving Federal Productivity, Publication (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: Human Resource Management: Status of Agency Practices for Improving Federal Productivity, 1987; Publication (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Implications of Electronic Mail for the Postal Service's Workforce, Publication (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: Implications for Electronic Mail for the Postal Service's Work Force, 1981; Publication (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office "Labor Contract Negotiations Under the Civil Service Reform Act of 1978", Publication (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: Labor Contract Negotiations Under the Civil Service Reform Act of 1978, 1984; Publication (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Proceedings of a Round Table Discussion on Product Quality--Japan v. the United States, Publication (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: Proceedings of a Round Table Discussion on Product Quality- Japan vs. the United States, 1981; Publication (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Productivity Sharing Programs: Can They Contribute to Productivity Improvement?, Publication (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: Productivity Sharing Programs: Can They Contribute to Productivity Improvement?, 1981; Publication (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Selected Government-Wide Management Improvement Efforts--1970-1980, Publication (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: Selected Government-Wide Management Improvement Efforts, 1983; Publication (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office "Report to Congressional Requesters", Publication (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Item 1: Health Care Spending Control, The Experience of France, Germany, and Japan, 1991; Publication (Box 25, Folder 69)
- United States General Accounting Office - Werneke, Diane., Publication (Box 26)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Steps Can Be Taken to Improve Federal Labor Management Relations and Reduce the Number and Costs of Unfair Labor Charges, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Steps Can be Taken to Improve Federal Labor-Management Relations and Reduce the Number and Costs of Unfair Labor Practice Charges, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, Stronger Federal Effort Needed to Foster Private Sector Productivity, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Stronger Federal Effort Needed to Foster Private Sector Productivity, 1981; Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, 'Sweatshops' in New York City: A Local Example of a Nationwide Problem, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Sweatshops in New York City: A Local Example of a Nationwide Problem, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office, "'Sweatshops' in the U.S.: Opinions and Their Extent and Possible Enforcement Options", Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Sweatshops in the U.S.: Opinions and Their Extent and Possible Enforcement Options, 1988; Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - U.S. General Service Administration, Communicator's Sourcebook: Tips and Tools for Speeches, Interviews and Press Conferences, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Communicator's Sourcebook:Tips and Tools for Speeches, Interviews, and Press Conferences, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - U.S. General Service Administration, End User Microcomputing: A Federal Survey Report and Resources Guide, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: End User Microcomputing: A Federal Survey Report and Resources Guide, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Merit Systems Protection Board, Getting Involved: Improving Federal Management, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Getting Involved: Improving Federal Management With Employee Participation, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - United States Postal Service and the National Rural Letter Carriers Association, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Guidelines: Quality of Work/Employee Involvement, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - USPS/NPOMH National Joint Committee on QWL. The Quality of Working Life Process, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: The Quality of Working Life Process, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - "Unemployment Compensation and Short-Time Compensation", Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Unemployment Compensation and Short-Time Compensation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Useem, Michael & Gottlieb, Martin M. "Corporate Restructuring, Ownership-Disciplined Alignment, and the Reorganization of Management, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Corporate Restructuring, Ownership-Disciplined Alignment, and the Reorganization of Management, 1990; Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
      Author: Michael Useem and Martin M. Gottlieb
  - Usilaner, Brian L., "The Continuing Need for Productivity Improvement", Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: The Continuing Need for Productivity Improvement, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
      Author: Brian L. Usilaner
  - Vanderporten, Bruce and W. Clayton Hall, "Conditions Leading to Collective Negotiations Among Police", Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Conditions Leading to Collective Negotiations Among Police, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
      Author: Bruce Vanderporten and W. Clayton Hall
  - Van Beinum, Hans, The Warp and Weft of QWL: On the Future of the Ontario QWL Centre, Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: The Warp and Weft of QWL: On the Future of the Ontario QWL Centre, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Van Beinum, Hans, What's in a Name: Playing Hide and Seek With QWL, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Van der Moolen, Rob, "Dutch 'Task Groups'", Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Van Horn, Carl E., Ken Ryan and William Tracy, Workforce Features: Strategic Planning in the States, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Workforce Futures: Strategic Planning in the States, 1990; Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
      Author: Carl E. Van Horn, Ken Ryan and William Tracy
  - Vaughan, Edward, "Structure and Strategy in the Case for Worker Participation", Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Structure and Strategy in the Case for Worker Participation, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
      Author: Edward Vaughan
  - Veld, Roelans J. "Education and Training: The Core Policies of Governments in Some Advanced Societies", Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Education and Training: The Core Policies of Governments in Some Advanced Societies, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
      Author: Roeland J. Veld
  - Verespej, Michael A., "Retraining for What?", Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Retraining for What?, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
      Author: Michael A. Verespej
  - Versespej, Michael A., "Wimpy: We'll Cooperate If", Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Wimpy: We'll Cooperate If, 1983; Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Verma, Anil, "Employee Involvement Programs: Do They Alter Worker Affinity Towards Unions?", Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Employee Involvement Programs: Do They Alter Worker Affinity Towards Unions?, 1986; Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
      Author: Anil Verma
  - Verman, Anil, "Joint-Participation Programs: Self-help or Suicide for Labor", Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Joint Participation Programs: Self-help or Suice for Labor?, 1989; Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
      Author: Anil verma
  - Versagi, Frank J., "What American Labor/Management can Learn From Japanese Unions", Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: What American labor/management can learn from Japanese unions, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
      Author: Frank J. Versagi
  - Victor, Kirk, "Labor Pains", Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Labor Pains, 1991; Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
      Author: Kirk Victor
  - Viscusi, W. Kip, "Strategic Behavior and the Impact of Unions on Wage Incentive Plans", Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Strategic Behavior and the Impact of Unions on Wage Incentive Plans, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
      Author: W. Kip Viscusi
  - Visions "Immigration Debate Spreads", Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Immigration Debate Spreads, 1990; Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Visser, Carla, "What We Can Learn from the Japanese About QCs", Publication (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: What We Can Learn from the Japanese About QCs, 1982; Publication (Box 26, Folder 28)
      Author: Carla Visser
  - Viswesvaran, Choklingham, Popejoy, Steven L., Deshpande, Satish. "Determinants of Managerialism: An Empirical Investigation", Publication (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Determinants of Managerialism: An Empirical Investigation, 1992; Publication (Box 26, Folder 29)
      Author: Chockalingam Viswesvaran, Steven L. Popejoy, Satish Deshpande
  - Vollmer, Rudolf J., "Labor Relations and Industrial Democracy in the Federal Republic of Germany", Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Labor Relations and Industrial Democracy in the Federal Republic of Germany, 1979; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
      Author: Rudolf J. Vollmer
  - Voos, Paula B., "Cooperative Labor Relations and the Collective Bargaining Environment", Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Cooperative Labor Relations and the Collective Bargaining Environment, 1985; Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
      Author: Paula B. Voos
  - Voos, Paula B., "The Impact of Programs to Improve Labor Relations on the Economic Performance of Unionized Companies", Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: The Impact of Programs to Improve Labor Relations on the Economic Performance of Unionized Companies, 1985; Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Voos, Paula B., "The Influence of Joint Committees and Other Labor Relations Programs on Union-Management Relations: An Analysis of Employers' Views", Publication (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: The Influence of Joint Committees and Other Labor Relations Programs on Union-Management Relations: An Analysis of Employers' Views, 1987; Publication (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Voos, Paula B., and Tsan-Yuang Cheng, "What Do Managers Mean by Cooperative Labor Relations?", Publication (Box 26, Folder 34)